French Painting Photograph Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- 19th – 20th century (18 photographs) (Box 18)
  - G (Box 106)
    - Gericault, Theodore, 1791-1824 (Box 111)
      - Paintings (22 photographs) (Box 111)
        - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 111)
          - A-P (27 photographs) (Box 111)
          - Q-Z (18 photographs) (Box 112)
        - Paris (46 photographs) (Box 112)
    - Gerome, Jean Leon, 1824-1904 (26 photographs) (Box 112)
      - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 113)
        - A-B (23 photographs) (Box 113)
        - O-Z (13 photographs) (Box 113)
    - Gilbert, Victor, 1847-1933 (7 photographs) (Box 113)
    - Gillot, Claude, 1673-1722 (9 photographs) (Box 113)
    - Girodet-Trioson, Anne Louis, 1767-1834 (28 photographs) (Box 113)
    - Gleizes, Albert, 1881-1953 (14 photographs) (Box 114)
    - Gleyre, Charles G., 1807-1874 (7 photographs) (Box 114)
    - Gonzales, Eva, 1849-1883 (8 photographs) (Box 114)
    - Granet, Francois Marius, 1775-1849 (14 photographs) (Box 114)
    - Greuze, Jean-Baptiste, 1725-1805 (Box 114)
      - Drawings (20 photographs) (Box 114)
      - Paintings (12 photographs) (Box 114)
        - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 114)
          - A-L (10 photographs (Box 114)
          - M-Z (16 photographs) (Box 115)
        - London (Box 115)
          - National Gallery (6 photographs) (Box 115)
          - Wallace Collection (19 photographs) (Box 115)
        - Paris (36 photographs) (Box 115)
    - Gromaire, Marcel, 1892- (10 photographs) (Box 116)
    - Gros, Antoine Jean, 1771-1835 (10 photographs) (Box 116)
      - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 116)
        - A-L (12 photographs) (Box 116)
        - M-Z (13 photographs) (Box 116)
        - Paris (24 photographs) (Box 116)
    - Gudin, Theodore, 1802-1880 (11 photographs) (Box 117)
    - Guerin, Pierre-Narcisse, 1774-1833 (23 photographs) (Box 117)
    - Guigou, Paul, 1834-1871 (6 photographs) (Box 117)
    - Guillaumin, Armand, 1841-1927 (29 photographs) (Box 117)
    - Guillonnet, Octave Denis Victor, 1872-1967 (10 photographs) (Box 117)
    - Guys, Constantin, 1805-1892 (10 photographs) (Box 117)
      - Miscellaneous Cities (24 photographs) (Box 118)
      - New York (Box 118)
  - H (Box 118)
    - Ha-He (8 photographs) (Box 118)
    - Ho-Hu (5 photographs) (Box 118)
    - Harpignies, Henri (28 photographs) (Box 118)
      - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 118)
        - A-L (3 photographs) (Box 118)
        - M-Z (8 photographs) (Box 119)
    - Hayet, Louis, 1864-1940 (9 photographs) (Box 119)
    - Helion, Jean, 1904- (6 photographs) (Box 119)
    - Henner, Jean Jacques, 1892-1905 (15 photographs) (Box 119)
    - Herbin, Auguste, 1883-1960 (15 photographs) (Box 119)
    - Hervier, Adolphe, 1818-1879 (5 photographs) (Box 119)
    - Huet, Jean Baptiste Marie, 1745-1811 (5 photographs) (Box 119)
    - Huet, Paul, 1803-1869 (20 photographs) (Box 119)
  - I (1 photograph) (Box 120)
    - Ingres, Jean-Auguste Dominique, 1780-1867 (Box 120)
      - Drawings (34 photographs) (Box 120)
        - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 120)
          - A-D (38 photographs) (Box 120)
          - E-Z Box 121 (17 photographs) (Box 121)
          - Montauban (14 photographs) (Box 121)
          - Paris (12 photographs) (Box 121)
      - Painting (13 photographs) (Box 121)
        - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 122)
          - A-F (32 photographs) (Box 122)
          - G-Z (26 photographs) (Box 122)
        - Aix-on-Provence (9 photographs) (Box 122)
        - Montauban (7 photographs) (Box 122)
        - New York (15 photographs) (Box 123)
        - Paris (4 photographs) (Box 123)
          - Louvre (38 photographs) (Box 123)
        - Washington (10 photographs) (Box 123)
    - Isabey, Eugene, 1803-1886 (12 photographs) (Box 123)
      - Miscellaneous Cities (26 photographs) (Box 124)
    - Isabey, Jean Baptiste, 1767-1855 (Box 124)
  - J-K (9 photographs) (Box 124)
    - Jacque, Charles Emil, 1813-1894 (6 photographs) (Box 124)
      - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 124)
        - A-O (14 photographs) (Box 124)
        - P-Z (17 photographs) (Box 124)
    - Jouvenet, Jean, 1644-1717 (7 photographs) (Box 125)
    - Klein, Yves (8 photographs) (Box 125)
  - L (Box 125)
    - La (33 photographs) (Box 125)
    - Le (34 photographs) (Box 125)
    - Li-Lu (8 photographs) (Box 126)
    - Lagneau, Nicolas, 1590-1666 (6 photographs) (Box 126)
    - Lagrenee, Louis Jean, 1724-1805 (11 photographs) (Box 126)
    - La Hyre, Laurent de, 1606-1656 (13 photographs) (Box 126)
    - Lamotte, Bernard (5 photographs) (Box 126)
    - Lami, Eugene (8 photographs) (Box 126)
    - Lancret, Nicolas, 1690-1743 (Box 126)
      - Drawings (14 photographs) (Box 126)
      - Paintings (21 photographs) (Box 127)
        - London (21 photographs) (Box 127)
        - Paris (13 photographs) (Box 127)
    - Largilliere, Nicolas de, 1656-1746 (42 photographs) (Box 128)
      - Paris (12 photographs) (Box 128)
    - Latouche, Gaston, 1854-1917 (8 photographs) (Box 128)
    - LaTour, Georges de, 1593-1652 (5 photographs) (Box 128)
      - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 129)
        - A-G (10 photographs) (Box 129)
        - H-Z (17 photographs) (Box 129)
      - Paris (12 photographs) (Box 129)
    - LaTour, Maurice Quentin de, 1704-1788 (Box 129)
      - Drawings (6 photographs) (Box 129)
      - Paintings (12 photographs) (Box 129)
        - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 129)
          - A-Z (14 photographs) (Box 129)
        - Paris (10 photographs) (Box 130)
    - Lauge, Achille, 1861-1944 (6 photographs) (Box 130)
    - Laurencin, Marie, 1883-1956 (32 photographs) (Box 130)
      - Private Collection (29 photographs) (Box 130)
        - Paris Box 131 (11 photographs) (Box 131)
    - Laurens, Henri, 1885-1954 (4 photographs) (Box 131)
    - Laurens, Jean Paul (6 photographs) (Box 131)
    - Lebasque, Henri, 1865-1937 (14 photographs) (Box 131)
    - Lebrun, Charles, 1619-1690 (10 photographs) (Box 131)
      - Paris (19 photographs) (Box 131)
    - Le Corbusier, 1887-1965 (Box 131)
    - Lefevre, Robert, 1755-1830 (6 photographs) (Box 132)
    - Leger, Fernand, 1881-1955 (Box 132)
      - Drawings (5 photographs) (Box 132)
      - Paintings (74 photographs) (Box 132)
        - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 133)
          - A-E (12 photographs) (Box 133)
          - F-O (15 photographs) (Box 133)
          - L-Z (12 photographs) (Box 133)
        - Biot (7 photographs) (Box 133)
        - New Haven (8 photographs) (Box 133)
        - New York (16 photographs) (Box 133)
        - Paris (25 photographs) (Box 134)
          - Galerie Louis Carre (8 photographs) (Box 134)
    - LeGros, Alphonse, 1837-1899 (7 photographs) (Box 134)
    - Lemordant, J-J. (7 photographs) (Box 134)
    - Le Moyne, Francois, 1688-1737 (9 photographs) (Box 134)
    - Lempicka, Tamara de, 1898- (7 photographs) (Box 134)
    - Le Nain, Antoine, 1588-1648 (3 photographs) (Box 134)
      - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 135)
        - A-L (20 photographs) (Box 135)
        - M-Z (34 photographs) (Box 135)
    - Lepicie, Nicolas-Bernard, 1735-1784 (8 photographs) (Box 135)
    - Lepine, Stanislas, 1836-1892 (6 photographs) (Box 135)
    - Le Sidanier, Henri, 1862-1939 (16 photographs) (Box 136)
    - Le Sueur, Eustache, 1617-1655 ( 8 photographs) (Box 136)
      - Paris (26 photographs) (Box 136)
    - Lhermitte, Leon-Augustin, 1844-1925 (19 photographs) (Box 136)
      - Miscellaneous Cities (10 photographs) (Box 137)
    - Lhote, Andre (9 photographs) (Box 137)
    - Lipchitz, Jacques, 1891- (5 photographs) (Box 137)
    - Loiseau, Gustave, 1865-1935 (7 photographs) (Box 137)
    - Loo, Charles Andre van, 1705-1765 (15 photographs) (Box 137)
    - Loo, Louis Michel van (10 photographs) (Box 137)
    - Lorrain (see Claude) (Box 138)
    - Loutherbourg, Philippe J. de, 1740-1812 (7 photographs) (Box 138)
    - Luce, Maximillen, 1858-1941 (7 photographs) (Box 138)
      - Miscellaneous Cities (18 photographs) (Box 138)
        - New York (12 photographs) (Box 138)
    - Lurcat, Jean, 1892- (10 photographs) (Box 138)
  - M (Box 139)
    - Ma-Ml (35 photographs) (Box 139)
    - Mo-Mz (22 photographs) (Box 139)
    - Maillol, Aristide, 1861-1944 (9 photographs) (Box 140)
    - Manet, Edouard, 1823-1883 (Box 140)
      - Drawings (66 photographs) (Box 140)
      - Drawings II (Box 141)
      - Paintings (29 photographs) (Box 141)
        - Private Collection (30 photographs) (Box 142)
          - Paul Mellon (10 photographs) (Box 142)
          - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 142)
            - A-D (21 photographs (Box 142)
            - E-N (24 photographs) (Box 143)
            - O-Z (18 photographs) (Box 143)
          - Boston (8 photographs) (Box 143)
          - Chicago (10 photographs) (Box 143)
          - Essen (5 photographs) (Box 143)
          - London (20 photographs) (Box 143)
          - Munich (8 photographs) (Box 144)
          - New York (28 photographs) (Box 144)
          - Paris (48 photographs) (Box 144)
          - Philadelphia (8 photographs) (Box 145)
          - Tournai (6 photographs) (Box 145)
          - Washington (20 photographs) (Box 145)
    - Manquin, Henri, 1874-1943 (12 photographs) (Box 145)
    - Marchand, Andre, 1877- (5 photographs) (Box 145)
    - Marilhat, Prosper, 1811-1847 (8 photographs) (Box 145)
    - Marmion, Simon, 1425-1489 (15 photographs) (Box 145)
    - Marquet, Albert, 1875-1947 (28 photographs) (Box 146)
      - Miscellaneous Cities (13 photographs) (Box 146)
      - Leningrad (17 photographs) (Box 146)
    - Martin, Henri, 1860-1943 (13 photographs) (Box 146)
    - Masquerier, John-James, 1778-1855 (9 photographs) (Box 146)
    - Masson, Andre, 1886-1987 (18 photographs) (Box 146)
    - Matisse, Henri, 1869-1954 (3 photographs) (Box 147)
      - Drawings (43 photographs) (Box 147)
        - Paper: Cut-outs (21 photographs) (Box 147)
      - Paintings (57 photographs) (Box 148)
        - Private Collection (76 photographs) (Box 148)
        - Private Collection II (Box 149)
          - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 149)
            - A-K (25 photographs) (Box 149)
            - L-Z (39 photographs) (Box 150)
          - Baltimore (12 photographs) (Box 150)
          - Copenhagen (17 photographs) (Box 150)
          - Leningrad (17 photographs) (Box 150)
          - New York (24 photographs) (Box 151)
          - Paris (28 photographs) (Box 151)
          - Washington (12 photographs) (Box 151)
    - Mexence, Edgard, 1871-1954 (5 photographs) (Box 151)
    - Meissonier, Jean Louise Ernest, 1815-1891 (Box 151)
      - Drawings (1 photograph) (Box 151)
      - Paintings (23 photographs) (Box 152)
        - London (17 photographs) (Box 152)
        - New York (10 photographs) (Box 152)
        - Paris (10 photographs) (Box 152)
    - Mellon, Claude, 1598-1688 (5 photographs) (Box 152)
    - Menard, Emil-Renee (6 photographs) (Box 152)
    - Mercie, Antonin, 1845-1916 (6 photographs) (Box 152)
    - Mercier, Philippe, 1689-1760 (6 photographs) (Box 152)
    - Meryon, Charles, 1821-1868 (12 photographs) (Box 153)
    - Metzinger, Jean, 1883-1956 (21 photographs) (Box 153)
    - Michallon, Achille Etna, 1796-1822 (17 photographs) (Box 153)
    - Michel, Georges, 1763-1843 (38 photographs) (Box 153)
    - Mignard, Pierre, 1610-1695 (25 photographs) (Box 154)
    - Millet, Jean-Francois, 1814-1875 (Box 154)
      - Drawings (65 photographs) (Box 154)
      - Drawings II (Box 155)
        - Private Collection (7 photographs) (Box 155)
          - Miscellaneous Cities (20 photographs) (Box 155)
          - Bayone (47 photographs) (Box 155)
          - Boston (16 photographs) (Box 156)
          - Chicago (17 photographs) (Box 156)
          - Cincinnati (4 photographs) (Box 156)
          - New Haven 14 photographs) (Box 156)
          - New York (11 photographs) (Box 156)
          - Paris (29 photographs) (Box 157)
          - Rotterdam (7 photographs) (Box 157)
          - Wayzata Minn. (8 photographs) (Box 157)
      - Paintings (38 photographs) (Box 158)
        Includes a folder of miscellaneous clippings.
        1 booklet (1908)
        - Private Collection 9 photographs (Box 158)
          - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 158)
            - A-M (32 photographs) (Box 158)
            - N-Z (25 photographs) (Box 159)
          - Boston (46 photographs) (Box 159)
          - Chicago (10 photographs) (Box 159)
          - Hague (6 photographs) (Box 160)
          - Paris (36 photographs) (Box 160)
    - Moillon, Louise, ca. 1610-ca. 1696 (5 photographs) (Box 160)
    - Monet, Claude, 1840-1926 (3 photographs) (Box 160)
      - Drawings (5 photographs) (Box 160)
      - Paintings (7 photographs) (Box 160)
        - Location unknown & Private Collection (Box 160)
        - Location unknown & Private Collection II (Box 161)
        - Location Unknown & Private Collection I (Box 162)
          - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 162)
            - A-C (30 photographs) (Box 162)
            - D-L (37 photographs) (Box 163)
            - M-P (28 photographs) (Box 163)
            - R-Z (31 photographs) (Box 163)
          - Basel (7 photographs) (Box 163)
          - Boston (80 photographs) (Box 164)
          - Chicago (21 photographs) (Box 164)
          - London (19 photographs) (Box 164)
          - New York (49 photographs) (Box 165)
          - Paris (57 photographs) (Box 165)
          - Washington (32 photographs) (Box 166)
    - Monnier, Henri, 1805-1877 (8 photographs) (Box 166)
    - Monticelli, Adolphe, 1824-1886 (45 photographs) (Box 166)
      - London (7 photographs) (Box 166)
      - Paris (4 photographs) (Box 166)
      - Washington (18 photographs) (Box 167)
    - Moreau, Gustave, 1826-1898 (28 photographs) (Box 167)
    - Moreau, Louis G, 1740-1806 (14 photographs) (Box 167)
      1 booklet (Deutsceh Kunst)
    - Moreau-Le-Jeune, JM, 1741-1814 (12 photographs) (Box 167)
    - Morisot, Berthe, 1841-1895 (Box 167)
      - Drawings (15 photographs) (Box 167)
      - Paintings (42 photographs) (Box 168)
    - Muenier, Jules, 1863-1942 (6 photographs) (Box 168)
  - N (4 photographs) (Box 168)
    - Nanteuil, Robert, 1623-1678 (4 photographs) (Box 168)
    - Natoire, Charles, 1700-1777 (10 photographs) (Box 168)
    - Nattier, Jean Marc, 1685-1766 (19 photographs) (Box 168)
      - Miscellaneous Cities (8 photographs) (Box 169)
      - London (6 photographs) (Box 169)
      - New York (4 photographs) (Box 169)
      - Paris (11 photographs) (Box 169)
      - Versailles (18 photographs) (Box 169)
      - Washington (5 photographs) (Box 169)
  - O (2 photographs) (Box 169)
    - Oudry, Jean Baptiste, 1686-1755 (23 photographs) (Box 169)
    - Ozenfant, Amédée, 1886-1966 (5 photographs) (Box 169)
  - P (Box 170)
    - Pa-Pe 922 photographs) (Box 170)
    - Pf-Pz (18 photographs) (Box 170)
    - Pascin, Jules, 1885-1930 (9 photographs) (Box 170)
    - Patel, Pierre, le père, 1605-1676 (3 photographs) (Box 170)
    - Pater, Jean Baptiste, 1695-1736 (Box 170)
      - Drawings (6 photographs) (Box 170)
      - Paintings (24 photographs) (Box 170)
      - London (12 photographs) (Box 171)
      - Paris (5 photographs) (Box 171)
      - Washington (5 photographs) (Box 171)
    - Perronneau, JB, 1715-1783 (15 photographs) (Box 171)
      - Paris (9 photographs) (Box 171)
    - Picabia, Francis, 1879-1953 (74 photographs) (Box 171)
      - Picabia II (Box 172)
    - Pissarro, Camille, 1831-1903 (Box 172)
      - Drawings (13 photographs) (Box 172)
      - Paintings (85 photographs) (Box 172)
        - Private Collections (23 photographs) (Box 173)
        - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 173)
          - A-H (28 photographs) (Box 173)
          - I-Z (22 photographs) (Box 173)
        - London (6 photographs) (Box 173)
        - New York (14 photographs) (Box 173)
        - Oxford (6 photographs) (Box 174)
        - Paris (27 photographs) (Box 174)
        - Washington (17 photographs) (Box 174)
    - Pissarro, Lucien, 1863-1944 (22 photographs) (Box 174)
    - Poliakoff, Serge, 1906-1969 (12 photographs) (Box 174)
    - Portail, Jacques André, 1695-1759 (4 photographs) (Box 174)
    - Poussin, Nicholas, 1594-1665 (Box 175)
      - Drawings (30 photographs) (Box 175)
      - Paintings (10 photographs) (Box 175)
        - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 175)
          - A-D (37 photographs) (Box 175)
          - E-Z (31 photographs) (Box 176)
        - Edinburgh (9 photographs) (Box 176)
        - Leningrad (14 photographs) (Box 176)
        - London (27 photographs) (Box 176)
        - New York (13 photographs) (Box 176)
        - Paris (59 photographs) (Box 177)
        - Philadelphia (5 photographs) (Box 177)
        - Rome (3 photographs) (Box 177)
        - Washington (12 photographs) (Box 177)
    - Prinet, René, 1861-1946 (3 photographs) (Box 178)
    - Prud'Hon, Pierre-Paul, 1758-1823 (Box 178)
      - Drawings (32 photographs) (Box 178)
      - Paintings (30 photographs) (Box 178)
        - Paris (13 photographs) (Box 178)
    - Pujol, Abelde, 1785-1861 (5 photographs) (Box 178)
    - Puvis de Chavannes, 1824-1898 (Box 179)
      - Drawings (13 photographs) (Box 179)
      - Paintings (20 photographs) (Box 179)
        - Miscellaneous Cities (22 photographs) (Box 179)
        - Boston (17 photographs) (Box 179)
        - Paris (20 photographs) (Box 179)
        - Washington (5 photographs) (Box 180)
  - Q (2 photographs) (Box 180)
  - R (Box 180)
    - Ra-Ri (23 photographs) (Box 180)
    - Rj-Rz (17 photographs) (Box 180)
    - Raffaelli, Jean François, 1850-1924 (24 photographs) (Box 180)
    - Ravier, Auguste François, 1814-1895 (6 photographs) (Box 180)
    - Redon, Odilon, 1840-1916 (41 photographs) (Box 181)
      - Miscellaneous Cities (48 photographs) (Box 181)
      - New York (14 photographs) (Box 181)
      - Paris (9 photographs) (Box 181)
    - Regnault, Henri, 1843-1871 (7 photographs) (Box 182)
    - Regnault, Jean Baptiste, 1754-1829 (6 photographs) (Box 182)
    - Regnier, Nicolas, 1590-1667 (4 photographs) (Box 182)
    - Renoir, Auguste, 1841-1919 (2 photographs) (Box 182)
      - Drawings (34 photographs) (Box 182)
      - Paintings (Box 182)
        - Location Unknown (Box 182)
        - Location Unknown II (107 photographs) (Box 183)
          - Private Collection I (40 photographs) (Box 183)
          - Private Collection II (Box 184)
            - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 184)
              - A-M (59 photographs) (Box 184)
              - N-Z (40 photographs) (Box 185)
            - Boston (10 photographs) (Box 185)
            - Chicago (16 photographs) (Box 185)
            - London (15 photographs) (Box 185)
            - Moscow (8 photographs) (Box 186)
            - New York (25 photographs) (Box 186)
              - Metropolitan Museum of Art (13 photographs) (Box 186)
            - Paris (29 photographs) (Box 186)
            - Philedelphia (10 photographs) (Box 186)
            - Washington (32 photographs) (Box 187)
    - Ribot, Théodule, 1823-1891 (22 photographs) (Box 187)
    - Rigaud, Hyacinthe, 1659-1743 (14 photographs) (Box 187)
      - Paris (19 photographs) (Box 187)
    - Robert, Hubert, 1733-1808 (Box 188)
      - Drawings (22 photographs) (Box 188)
      - Paintings (30 photographs) (Box 188)
        - Miscellaneous Cities (28 photographs) (Box 188)
        - New York (8 photographs) (Box 189)
        - Paris (14 photographs) (Box 189)
    - Robert, Leopold, 1794-1835 (4 photographs) (Box 189)
    - Rodin, Auguste, 1840-1917 (12 photographs) (Box 189)
      - New Haven (28 photographs) (Box 189)
      - Paris (28 photographs) (Box 189)
      - Paris II (Box 190)
    - Rolle, Alfred-Phillipe, 1846-1919 (5 photographs) (Box 190)
    - Roqueplan, Camille, 1800-1855 (5 photographs) (Box 190)
    - Roslin, Alexander, 1718-1793 (6 photographs) (Box 190)
    - Roualt, Georges, 1871-1958 (4 photographs) (Box 190)
      - Location Unknown (39 photographs) (Box 190)
      - Private Collection (18 photographs) (Box 191)
        - Miscellaneous Cities (11 photographs) (Box 191)
        - New York (14 photographs) (Box 191)
        - Paris (13 photographs) (Box 191)
    - Rousseau, Henri, 1844-1910 (16 photographs) (Box 191)
      - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 191)
        - A-L (14 photographs) (Box 191)
        - M-Z 13 photographs) (Box 192)
      - New York (16 photographs) (Box 192)
      - Paris 13 photographs) (Box 192)
      - Washington (9 photographs) (Box 192)
    - Rousseau, Théodore, 1812-1867 (Box 192)
      - Drawings (10 photographs) (Box 192)
      - Paintings (23 photographs) (Box 192)
        - Miscellaneous Cities (39 photographs) (Box 192)
        - Miscellaneous Cities II (Box 193)
        - Cincinnati (11 photographs) (Box 193)
        - The Hague (10 photographs) (Box 193)
        - London (11 photographs) (Box 193)
        - Paris (15 photographs) (Box 193)
    - Roussel, Ker-Xavier, 1867-1944 (5 photographs) (Box 193)
    - S (40 photographs) (Box 194)
    - Saint-Aubin, Gabriel de, 1724-1780 (Box 194)
      - Drawings (18 photographs) (Box 194)
      - Paintings (6 photographs) (Box 194)
    - Scheffer, Ary, 1795-1858 (24 photographs) (Box 194)
    - Segonzac, André de, 1884-1974 (30 photographs) (Box 195)
    - Seguin, Armand, 1869-1903 (4 photographs) (Box 195)
    - Sérusier, Paul, 1864-1927 (8 photographs) (Box 195)
      - Drawings (57 photographs) (Box 195)
      - Drawings II (Box 196)
      - Paintings (18 photographs) (Box 196)
        - Miscellaneous Cities (31 photographs) (Box 196)
        - Chicago (14 photographs) (Box 196)
        - London (32 photographs) (Box 196)
        - New York (32 photographs) (Box 197)
        - Otterlo (10 photographs) (Box 197)
        - Paris (15 photographs) (Box 197)
        - Washington (16 photographs) (Box 197)
    - Signac, Paul, 1863-1935 (Box 197)
      - Drawings (7 photographs) (Box 197)
      - Paintings (49 photographs) (Box 198)
        - New York (9 photographs) (Box 198)
        - Otterlo (9 photographs) (Box 198)
        - Paris (7 photographs) (Box 198)
    - Singier, Gustave, 1909-1984 (6 photographs) (Box 198)
    - Sisley, Alfred, 1839-1899 (67 photographs) (Box 198)
      - Miscellaneous Cities (71 photographs) (Box 199)
      - New York (9 photographs) (Box 199)
      - Paris (23 photographs) (Box 200)
      - Washington (8 photographs) (Box 200)
    - Soulanges, Pierre, 1919-1963 (18 photographs) (Box 200)
    - Soutine, Chaim, 1893-1943 (20 photographs) (Box 200)
      - Miscellaneous Cities (25photographs) (Box 200)
      - London (9 photographs) (Box 200)
      - New York (31 photographs) (Box 201)
      - Paris (13 photographs) (Box 201)
    - Souverbie, Jean, 1891- (3 photographs) (Box 201)
    - Staël, Nicolas de, 1914-1955 (32 photographs) (Box 201)
    - Steinlen, Théophile A, 1859-1923 (5 photographs) (Box 201)
    - Stella, Jacques, 1596-1657 (5 photographs) (Box 201)
    - Subleyras, Pierre, 1699-1749 (13 photographs) (Box 201)
      - Paris (11 photographs) (Box 202)
  - T (16 photographs) (Box 202)
    - Tanguy, Yves, 1900-1955 (Box 202)
      - Drawings (11 photographs) (Box 202)
      - Paintings (26 photographs) (Box 202)
    - Tassaert, NFO, 1800-1874 (9 photographs) (Box 202)
    - Tissot, James, 1836-1902 (48 photographs) (Box 202)
    - Tissot II (Box 203)
    - Tocqué, Louis, 1696-1772 (11 photographs) (Box 203)
      - Paris (4 photographs) (Box 203)
    - Toulouse-Lautrec, 1864-1901 (Box 203)
      - Drawings (19 photographs) (Box 203)
        - Williamstown (7 photographs) (Box 203)
      - Paintings (31 photographs) (Box 203)
        - Miscellaneous Cities (28 photographs) (Box 204)
        - Albi (22 photographs) (Box 204)
        - Chicago (12 photographs) (Box 204)
        - New York (20 photographs) (Box 204)
        - Paris (15 photographs) (Box 204)
        - Philadelphia (6 photographs) (Box 205)
        - Washington (10 photographs) (Box 205)
    - Trouillebert, Paul Dèsiré, 1829-1900 (7 photographs) (Box 205)
    - Troy, Jean François de, 1679-1752 (17 photographs) (Box 205)